<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Ali Khalili</title>
    <link>https://alikhalili.me/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Ali Khalili</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 25 Jun 2020 13:48:21 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://alikhalili.me/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Configure Prometheus with Appmetrics in ASP.NET Core</title>
      <link>https://alikhalili.me/blog/posts/appmetrics-prometheus-grafana-asp-core/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Jun 2020 13:48:21 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alikhalili.me/blog/posts/appmetrics-prometheus-grafana-asp-core/</guid>
      <description>One of a super crucial part of each application obviously is metrics, first of all, we need to figure it out what actually metric means and make a distinction between metrics and logging. I don&amp;rsquo;t want to go through details however metric represents everything related to the numbers, basically, if you have numerical stuff, it would be involved with metrics as well; in other hand loggings come with some human readable information such as &amp;ldquo;Order was inserted with these parameters lablablab ;)&amp;rdquo; I guess it&amp;rsquo;s clear enough right now, so in case of having some sort of numbers as same as request counts, CPU or memory consumptions, etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OWIN and ASP.NET CORE</title>
      <link>https://alikhalili.me/blog/posts/owin-asp-net-core/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jun 2020 13:21:04 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alikhalili.me/blog/posts/owin-asp-net-core/</guid>
      <description>If you have followed the last article regarding process of migrating to asp.net core, we had been discussing a lot about OWIN and its usage amid this goal, I just wanna quickly let you know how easily you can share all your previous codes into asp.net core as well, keep tuned ;)
How is it possible to use OWIN pipeline in Asp.net core? is it? The answer is pretty straight forward: yes!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Migrating to ASP.NET CORE!</title>
      <link>https://alikhalili.me/blog/posts/migrating-to-asp-net-core/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 May 2020 14:49:18 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alikhalili.me/blog/posts/migrating-to-asp-net-core/</guid>
      <description>Hi! I&amp;rsquo;ve prepared some personal experiences regarding updating an old fashioned asp .net mvc to brand new asp .net core
How? Of course it&amp;rsquo;s going to be controversial and it&amp;rsquo;s not black and white, but I&amp;rsquo;ve been trying to gather appropriate information involving with my knowledge during the past couple of years to show you guys how you are able to get rid of your old app and move to .</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>